<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>UXPA UT Austin</title>
    <link>https://uxpa.ischool.utexas.edu/</link>
    <description>Recent content on UXPA UT Austin</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <managingEditor>uxpautaustin@gmail.com (Brent Biglin)</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>uxpautaustin@gmail.com (Brent Biglin)</webMaster>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 31 Aug 2017 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://uxpa.ischool.utexas.edu/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>New Student Spotlight</title>
      <link>https://uxpa.ischool.utexas.edu/post/2017-08-31-ali-funnell/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 Aug 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>uxpautaustin@gmail.com (Brent Biglin)</author>
      <guid>https://uxpa.ischool.utexas.edu/post/2017-08-31-ali-funnell/</guid>
      <description>Ali Funnell Hi, everyone! My name is Ali Funnell, I’m a first-year student at the iSchool, interested in pursuing a path in User Experience/User Interface Design.
My first exposure to the term ‘UX/UI’ was during a networking event. As I listened to a speaker enthusiastically describe human-computer interaction and user interface design, it sparked something inside me. The synthesis of technology and design in a field applicable to a broad range of industries excited me.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>First Post!</title>
      <link>https://uxpa.ischool.utexas.edu/post/2017-06-28-first-post/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Jun 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>uxpautaustin@gmail.com (Brent Biglin)</author>
      <guid>https://uxpa.ischool.utexas.edu/post/2017-06-28-first-post/</guid>
      <description>Brent Biglin: After attending the UXPA International Conference for the first time this past year, Kelsey Belcher, Eric Graham, Kathryn Golden, and I decided to start one of the first UXPA student chapters at the University of Texas at Austin. We&amp;rsquo;ve met the past two weeks on Tuesday evenings to sort out our charter and bylaws in order to start taking members and creating events for the Fall 2017 semester.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Board Members</title>
      <link>https://uxpa.ischool.utexas.edu/page/board-members/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>uxpautaustin@gmail.com (Brent Biglin)</author>
      <guid>https://uxpa.ischool.utexas.edu/page/board-members/</guid>
      <description> UXPA UT Austin Chapter Board  Brent Biglin – Communications Lead Kelsey L Belcher – Events Lead Bria Fowler - Social Media Lead Eric T Graham – Outreach Lead Kathryn E Golden – Memberships Lead Dixie Hamilton - Operations Lead  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Events</title>
      <link>https://uxpa.ischool.utexas.edu/page/events/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>uxpautaustin@gmail.com (Brent Biglin)</author>
      <guid>https://uxpa.ischool.utexas.edu/page/events/</guid>
      <description>For regular event announcements, join our UT Listserv. October 9-13, Austin Human Factors and Ergonomics Society International Annual Meeting Gain new knowledge and network with colleagues at the HFES 2017 International Annual Meeting, which features more than 130 concurrent sessions, plus interactive posters and demos, Fellows posters, and the sixth User Experience Day, featuring a dedicated program track. Take away the latest research and practice solutions from 24 technical areas.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Join</title>
      <link>https://uxpa.ischool.utexas.edu/page/become-a-member/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>uxpautaustin@gmail.com (Brent Biglin)</author>
      <guid>https://uxpa.ischool.utexas.edu/page/become-a-member/</guid>
      <description>Register here! To join the User Experience Professionals Association of UT Austin, all you have to do is be a student of UT Austin and have an interest in user experience design, research, and evaluation. While not required to be a member of our chapter, becoming a member of UXPA International is required in order to be a voting member or board member.
Our goal is to create events and programs to benefit the UX community at the iSchool and UT in general, as well as to connect our students with the international UX community through UXPA International.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>UXPA International</title>
      <link>https://uxpa.ischool.utexas.edu/page/uxpa/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>uxpautaustin@gmail.com (Brent Biglin)</author>
      <guid>https://uxpa.ischool.utexas.edu/page/uxpa/</guid>
      <description>The User Experience Professionals Association is a network for user experience professionals across the world who design, research, and evaluate products and services. UXPA holds an international conference every year, publishes through the Journal of Usability Studies and User Experience Magazine, and has more than 50 chapters around the world.
UXPA&amp;rsquo;s stated goals are to:
 Become the authoritative source on the practice of usability, user-centered design (UCD), and user experience.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>