<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Pages on UXPA UT Austin</title>
    <link>https://uxpa.ischool.utexas.edu/page/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Pages on UXPA UT Austin</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <managingEditor>uxpautaustin@gmail.com (Brent Biglin)</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>uxpautaustin@gmail.com (Brent Biglin)</webMaster>
    
	<atom:link href="https://uxpa.ischool.utexas.edu/page/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Board Members</title>
      <link>https://uxpa.ischool.utexas.edu/page/board-members/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>uxpautaustin@gmail.com (Brent Biglin)</author>
      <guid>https://uxpa.ischool.utexas.edu/page/board-members/</guid>
      <description> UXPA UT Austin Chapter Board  Brent Biglin – Communications Lead Kelsey L Belcher – Events Lead Bria Fowler - Social Media Lead Eric T Graham – Outreach Lead Kathryn E Golden – Memberships Lead Dixie Hamilton - Operations Lead  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Events</title>
      <link>https://uxpa.ischool.utexas.edu/page/events/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>uxpautaustin@gmail.com (Brent Biglin)</author>
      <guid>https://uxpa.ischool.utexas.edu/page/events/</guid>
      <description>For regular event announcements, join our UT Listserv. Wednesday, September 13 Member Meeting Time: 6:00pm - 7:30pm Location: UTA 1.208 Join us our first ever member meeting. Meet other UXers and learn about our Peer Mentorship Program, in addition to other events and programs like workshops, guest speakers, and portfolio working groups. September 15-17 Women Who Code: ATX Diversity Hackathon Women Who Code is providing a space for people of all backgrounds who want to start building their tech portfolio or finish up a tech project while learning new skills.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Join</title>
      <link>https://uxpa.ischool.utexas.edu/page/become-a-member/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>uxpautaustin@gmail.com (Brent Biglin)</author>
      <guid>https://uxpa.ischool.utexas.edu/page/become-a-member/</guid>
      <description>Register here! To join the User Experience Professionals Association of UT Austin, all you have to do is be a student of UT Austin and have an interest in user experience design, research, and evaluation. While not required to be a member of our chapter, becoming a member of UXPA International is required in order to be a voting member or board member.
Our goal is to create events and programs to benefit the UX community at the iSchool and UT in general, as well as to connect our students with the international UX community through UXPA International.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>UXPA International</title>
      <link>https://uxpa.ischool.utexas.edu/page/uxpa/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>uxpautaustin@gmail.com (Brent Biglin)</author>
      <guid>https://uxpa.ischool.utexas.edu/page/uxpa/</guid>
      <description>The User Experience Professionals Association is a network for user experience professionals across the world who design, research, and evaluate products and services. UXPA holds an international conference every year, publishes through the Journal of Usability Studies and User Experience Magazine, and has more than 50 chapters around the world.
UXPA&amp;rsquo;s stated goals are to:
 Become the authoritative source on the practice of usability, user-centered design (UCD), and user experience.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>